Now we are seeing videos, but before any video, there's pre-production.
What is pre-production for a music video?
Well, that's all the effort, time, energy and planning that goes into making that video.
You know, your thoughts on where we're going to shoot this video?
How are we going to shoot it?
What's going to be the location?
What type of things do we want to use?
As far as, what type of props will we use?
Backdrops, lighting, will there be a day video, night video?
Are we going to use a story line, guideline, these type of things.
And far as in mind, you know, the budget, that you're allowed to spend with, you know, whether how much money can be used in shooting this video.
Casting forward; who do we want in this video?
Where do we want, where do we want go?
What kind of feel do we want for it?
All of these things are the things that take place before video takes place.
You know, before anything comes to bout, it always starts as an idea and that basically what pre-production of a video is.
So next time you're watching that video, or maybe you're thinking about making your video, just remember the most important thing of a video is the pre-production of a video.
Peace!